[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country leads the world in per capita beer consumption:", "correct_answer": "The Czech Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["Ireland", "The UK", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the leader of the villains that come to earth in the 1978 movie Superman?", "correct_answer": "General Zod", "incorrect_answers": ["Jor-El", "Non", "Clark Kent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these seas surrounds the Korean Peninsula, in the northern part of which North Korea is located?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["East China Sea", "Sea of Japan", "Yellow Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What goes wrong at the airport when Greg and Pamela take the plane at the the beginning of the 2004 movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Greg loses his suitcase.", "Pam breaks her heel.", "A baby vomits on Gregs shoulder."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what century was the first form of the lighter created?", "correct_answer": "16th century", "incorrect_answers": ["2nd century", "6th century", "10th century"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed, which appeared naturally in Thailand, has a slim body and short fur with point coloration.", "correct_answer": "Siamese", "incorrect_answers": ["Himalayan", "Korat", "Burmese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Donald Sutherland played Joseph T. Wladislaw in The Dirty Dozen.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for his performance in a 1999 movie.", "correct_answer": "Adam Sandler for Big Daddy", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Kline for Wild Wild West", "Arnold Schwarzenegger for End of Days", "Robin Williams for Bicentennial Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Willem J. Kolff credited for inventing?", "correct_answer": "Artificial kidneys and artificial heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Computer", "Heart-Lung machine", "CAT scan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A dog should never be left with a child under this age because the child may injure the dog or him/herself.", "correct_answer": "five", "incorrect_answers": ["ten", "seven", "three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which President ended Reconstruction ?", "correct_answer": "Hayes", "incorrect_answers": ["Grant", "Garfield", "Arthur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This director, who made 1986s Down and Out in America and 1976s The Stronger, was blacklisted in 1951 by the House Un-American Activities Committee.", "correct_answer": "Lee Grant", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed Wood", "Gore Verbinski", "Paul Greengrass"]}]